hisunglasses.com 2007-12-24

# Sunglasses. Designer Sunglasses by Chanel, Oakley, & Gucci. Discount Sunglasses

Privacy at HiSunglasses.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our web site visitors and clients. We uphold the highest industry standards in online privacy and permission marketing. 

**Security and Privacy:**

HiSunglasses uses security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We store the information in a database in a secure environment at our data center. 

We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you e-mails based on your requesting information. 

**Information Tracked:**

At times we will use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. We also may track browser types to help us understand our visitors' needs related to our web site design. 

There is an optional section of our web site where input forms require your name, company, and e-mail address. This form provides the ability to opt-in to receiving future emails of any sort from HiSunglasses. If you opt-in to receiving email communications from us, then we may send information to you on our products or services. 

You may review and change your information with us at any time by Loging in to your account or by contacting us at support@HiSunglasses.com 

**Cookies:**

Client-side cookies are used to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site; however, the user may not be able to access all areas of our site. 

**Links to other Websites:**

HiSunglasses is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites to which we link. 

**Notification of Changes:**

HiSunglasses.com will notify its members and users via email if we make any changes to our privacy policy. Any new policy will be posted on our site at least one week prior to its taking effect. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or this web site, please contact us at: support@HiSunglasses.com.
